soapcentral.com 2012-06-16

# Privacy Statement | soapcentral.com @ soapcentral.com

Thank you for visiting the **soap** central **.com** site. Your privacy is important to us. In an effort to better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices of collecting and disseminating information. 

THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT   
Throughout the **soap** central **.com** site, you can enter contests, expression your opinions on message boards and forums, vote in polls, or subscribe to any or all of our newsletters. In order to access these features we ask that you supply us with personally identifiable information such as name, email address, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs and services. 

At some areas of the **soap** central **.com** site, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you choose to send a Soap Card (an electronic postcard), you might submit the recipient's name and email address. In this situation, the recipient's email address is required. 

The **soap** central **.com** message boards feature an option that allows individual users to determine if they would like to share (display) their email address with other board visitors. This decision is up to you, the user, who will have the option to post your email address on and or all messages that you post. By default, the "Do Not Display My email Address" has been selected for all posters. 

We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows '95 or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink). 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. The third-party advertising technology that we use on this Web site uses information derived from your visits to this site to target advertising within this site. In addition, our advertisers may use other third-party advertising technology to target advertising on this site and other sites. In the course of advertisements being served to you, a unique third-party cookie or cookies may be placed your browser. In addition, we use Web beacons, provided by third-party advertising companies, to help manage and optimize our online advertising. Web beacons enable us to recognize a browser's cookie when a browser visits this site, to learn which banner ads bring users to our Web site and to deliver more relevant advertising. To "opt-out," please click here. http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/index.aspx. 

HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT   
First and foremost, the information we collect is used to enhance all of our visitor's experiences on the **soap** central **.com** web site. 

Another key aspect of collecting information, such as name and email address, is so that we can respond to the users of our site when they have technical problems or questions about a feature or other aspect of the web site. 

We use the information that you provide about others to enable us to send them your gifts or cards. From time to time, we also may use this information to offer our products, programs, or services to them. 

The information we collect in connection with our online forums and communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities and, from time to time, to offer you products, programs, or services. 

On occasion, we may use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the performance, design and content of our site. This information may also enable us to personalize your visits to the site and provide you with content and information that most interests you. 

By collecting non-personally identifiable information, we are also able to determine which features of the site are most visited. This information may be used to determine which features to enhance or remove from the site. We also may disclose such information to a third-party for advertising purposes. 

We will disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request. 

Representatives, agents and contractors of **soap** central **.com** who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a matter that is consistent with this Privacy Notice. For example, these parties may not use this information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for **soap** central **.com**. 

THIRD-PARTY AND SPONSOR SITES   
Some areas of **soap** central **.com** contain links to other Internet sites whose information practices may be different their ours. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. 

**soap** central **.com** sometimes may offer contests, sweepstakes, or promotions that are sponsored by or co-sponsored with identified third parties. By virtue of their sponsorship, these third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the contest, sweepstakes, or promotion. **soap** central **.com** has no control over the third-party sponsors' use of this information. **soap** central **.com** will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if third-party sponsors will obtain such information. 

COOKIES   
Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering for one of our contests, the message board or other features that require the use of an email address. 

We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g. to recognize you by name when you return to our site), save your password in password-protected areas, and enable you to use shopping carts on our sites. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services. 

COMMITTED TO SECURITY   
We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online. 

WHAT TO DO IF YOUR INFORMATION NEEDS TO BE UPDATED OR CORRECTED   
Instructions on how to edit any of your personally identifiable information is available at the point of collection. Should you need to correct or edit any of your personally identifiable information, you may contact us by Feedback. For verification purposes please include your first name, last name, e-mail address and the password you use on the **soap** central **.com** site. 

HOW TO CONTACT US   
If you have any questions or concerns about the **soap** central **.com** Privacy Policy or its implementation you may contact us by Feedback.
